said battery how are you today how are my
dicha batería cómo está hoy cómo está mi
kids show your tattoo well
chavalería enseña tu tatuaje pues
wait first I'm going to put the cap
espérate primero voy a poner la gorra
forward we can go see here the
para alante podemos ir viendo aquí la
camera with the cap backwards and I went from
cámara con la gorra para atrás y pasó de
recording the video with the cap backward
grabar el vídeo con la gorra para atrás
because I'm going to look like Frank Cuesta or
porque me voy a parecer frank cuesta o
something it doesn't seem like I fell for it finishing the
algo no parece que me cayera acabando la
boy and I was half mongol but what I'm
chico y me quedé medio mongol pero lo
never going to do is put my
que no voy a hacer nunca es ponerme la
cap sideways like his brother puts it
gorra así de lado como se la pone el su
in his hands records videos like that and
hermano en sus manos graba videos así y
expects us to take it seriously I already
pretende que lo tomemos en serio ya
regretted having
bastante me arrepentido de haberme
scraped your guilt of the 700 thousand
raspamos vuestra culpa de los 700 mil
light so I have to be with a cap what do you
light así que tengo que estar con gorra
think my precious pompadour and I
está que me crees que mi precioso tupé y
'm going to record with the one about bumping before and I got a
voy a grabar con el de topar antes y me
tattoo I got a tattoo it's not that I'm
tatuado me tatuado no es que esté
showing off the tattoo and showing off my
presumiendo el tatuaje y presumiendo de
biceps my friends you know why I have
bíceps mis panas sabéis porque llevo
n't uploaded videos since Thursday I was worried
desde el jueves sin subir vídeos me daba
if I didn't think I would say no so as not to
lo que si no pensaba decir no para no
worry you all I've been in the hospital
preocuparos he estado en el hospital
admitted I've hurt my back a lot
ingresado me he hecho mucho daño en la
carrying all my charisma and
espalda cargando con todo mi carisma y
my talent is  that you guys think it's
mi talento es que ustedes se creen que
easy to carry this forward but this
es fácil llevar esto pa lante pero esto
is its thing this costs its thing in my
está lo suyo esto cuesta lo suyo en mis
friends is that you always look
panas es que ustedes siempre se os ve
very fresh having made me status but there hasn't been
muy fresco haberme hecho status pero no
time obviously to
ha dado tiempo evidentemente de
finish it because like in a big way we have
terminarlo porque así en plan grande
also been reviewing the
hemos estado repasando también los
previous ones that needed a review I have
anteriores que hacía falta un repasito
to
tengo que
this week I have to follow this has to
esta semana tengo que seguir esto tiene
color it all my friend tattoo artist I'm
que colorearlo entero mi pana tatuador
going to give you the tattoo artist's Instagram
os voy a dar el instagram del tatuador
in case you like the tattoos that you go you're
por si os mola los tatuajes que vayáis
going to go all over the world and you're going to
vais a ir todo el mundo y le vais a
follow him on Instagram if you like
seguir en instagram si os gustan los
tattoos light and also you're going to see when
tatuajes leve y además vais a ver cuando
I was treated determined you're going to see it
se me trató determinado lo vais a ver
uploaded there and I'm going to say wow how
allí subido y vaya a decir guau que
fresh my friend Javi looks with success
fresco se le ve a mi pana javi con éxito
you know that I'm going to go to the whole sleeves
ya sabes que me voy a las mangas entera
and the whole roll in fact these are extreme I
y todo el rollo de hecho estas extreme
also have an appointment to tattoo on my
también tengo cita para tatuar en la
hand
mano
I'm going to be really cool so that you follow the
voy a molar un montón para que sigáis el
guy I
chico
am decided to do that I wanted because a
soy decidí hacer que yo quería porque un
dog because I was going to be treated by a dog
perro porque me iba a tratar un perro
Pablo Vargas because a dog hey well
pablo vargas porque un perro oye pues
look because I'm a big fan of  the magazine
mira porque soy muy fan de la revista
house with your dog because I was going to take
casa con tu perro porque me iba a tomar
a dog that asks is that one that sometimes
un perro que pregunta es esa que a veces
seems to go [ __ ] it seems and the chat
parece ir subnormales parece y el chat
of the live shows of win bischoff and me and
de los directos de win bischoff y yo y
my dog
mi perrito
[Music]
[Música]
well but because I think he gets
bueno pero porque yo creo que se ofende
a little offended when when I say dog
un poco cuando cuando le digo perro
we are here assuming his gender by the
estamos aquí asumiendo su género por la
face and my dog ​​of my little
cara y mi perro de mi perrita por el
dog because of the coolness he doesn't want to see a tattoo with 23 in the second I believed a tattoo go from me and they are going to attend to them very cool the thing that I was proposing to you today the fact of making a video that is very fashionable in some
vídeo que está muy de moda en algunos
youtube channels which is to make a
canales de youtube que es hacer una
lollipop and compete cannot be done
piruleta y competir no puede hacerse
according to a gear list a very
según externó una gear list una tía muy
smart girl is a very smart girl and the
lista es una tía muy lista y se puntúa
highest score is given to whoever is the best and it goes down
más alto a quien sea mejor y va bajando
and down and we are going to do it my friends
y bajando y lo vamos a hacer mis panas
because we are here very fresh and since there are
porque estamos aquí muy frescos y ya que
not many in seo then surely we are
no hay muchos al seo pues seguramente lo
going to form it making this land
vamos a formar haciendo esta tierra
because surely I am going to release
porque seguramente voy a soltar alguna
something from some youtube which is not going to
cosa de algún youtube el que no le va a
be thanks to your fund or they are going to come to me
ser gracias a su fund o me van a venir a
put [ __ ] and a roll that we
meter [__] y un rollo de que la
do it I would say that it is from youtuber
hacemos yo diría que es de youtuber
obviously not I think it is clear
evidentemente no yo creo que está claro
why I would not be from cookies of
por qué no lo había ser de galletas de
Spain nor am I going to be from fast food
españa ni la voy a ser de comida rápida
nor am I going to be much less from a
ni la voy a ser mucho menos de partido
political party of Spain do not you see it is
político de españa no lo veis lo está
for the chat but that would be good that
para el chat pero eso sería bueno eso
would be clear not at 130 letters you already
estaría claro no a 130 letras ya me
know me my friends let's see where the thing about
conocéis mis panas a ver dónde está lo
the youtubers is there you get the
de los youtubers ahí te salen aquí los
youtube here I shut up
youtube callo
all of you a list of youtube that
a todos ustedes una lista de youtube que
are from youtube that we know it
sean de youtube que nosotros sabemos
said youtube spain
ponía youtube españa
[Music]
[Música]
here is today's video I hope you
ya está aquí el vídeo de hoy espero que
liked it guys until
os haya gustado chavales hasta el
next time no seriously there is no list of
próximo no en serio no hay una lista de
youtube that people know to see it would be
youtube que la gente conozca a ver sería
the top decent genius indifferent bad
el top genio decente indiferente malo
horrible dallas I
horrible dallas
can't record this video like I recorded
no puedo grabar este vídeo como yo grabé
this video sending even the divorce
este vídeo mandando hasta el divorcio
what is wrong with these people why do they put dallas on
qué pasa con esta gente porque ponen en
this page at the lowest level they
esta página en el nivel más bajo a
are allies can it be changed can it be
dallas son aliados se puede cambiar se
changed what would we put down here
puede cambiar que pondríamos aquí abajo
removed we put removed the quality is
quitó ponemos quitó la calidad es
quality is I think in the worst
calidad es yo creo que en la peor
category alevín well indifferent and is going to
categoría alevín bueno indiferente y va
put it in bad for the attitude he
a ponerlo en malos por la actitud que
had do you remember the video we made
tuvo os acordáis el vídeo que le hicimos
when suddenly a corner is freed and
cuando de repente se libra una esquina y
enjoying there right and left the
disfrutar ahí a diestro y siniestro el
capo of the field seems horrible to me
capo del campo me parece horrible
sincerely I know that I know that she earns me
sinceramente sé que sé que ella me gana
a lot of dislike but I'm going to be honest
mucho dislike pero yo voy a ser sincero
Vanessa seems horrible to me he seems like a
vanessa me parece horrible me parece un
guy who entertains us I have
tío que que nos divierte yo lo he
tried to understand trying to get into
intentado comprender intentado meterse
his live streams and say I'm going to
meterme en sus directos y decir voy a
try to understand why these people
intentar comprender por qué esta gente
suck his balls so much and
le chupan tanto los huevos y
honestly it's not fun he starts
sinceramente no es divertido se pone a
shouting in his live streams from time to time he gets
gritar en sus directos de vez en cuando
angry he starts insulting people I
se cabrea empieza a insultar a la peña o
mean no
sea no
this guy the truth is that I would put him
este chico la verdad que lo pondría en
indifferent but I'm going to put him in bad
indiferente pero lo voy a poner en malo
because he participated in an
porque participó en una campaña de
advertising campaign for rice you are already this is
publicidad de arroz sos ya este es
your idols go to Mercadona to
vuestro ídolos a vais al mercadona a
buy and in it
comprar y en él
the rice no the package of rum was not I
el arroz no el paquete de ron no era
think it was
creo que era de comida de estas
precooked food no no no it was not the rice no I don't
precocinada no no no no era el arroz no
remember but come on in any
no me acuerdo pero vamos en cualquier
food from Mercadona you cannot
alimento del mercadona no puedes
appear  in a box
aparecer en una caja
peter to peter I seem totally
peter a peter me parece totalmente
indifferent, I really like this guy
indiferente este muchacho me cae muy
to do now this guy
bien a realizar ahora este muchacho se
seems very fresh to my friend he seems very
le ve muy fresco a mi pana se le ve muy
nice and I like him I like how he
agradable y me gusta me gusta cómo
interacts with his audience so I'm going
interactúa con su público así que lo voy
to put it in decent I think he's a guy who
a poner en decente me parece un tío que
has opened up a lot with his audience and
se ha abierto bastante con su público y
I like this alpha guy also I
me mola este chico alfa además lo
know him and I really like him all the
conozco y me caes de la madre a todos
youtubers that I know and can talk
los youtubers que conozco y can habla
to him they like him a lot I'm going to put him
con él les cae muy bien lo voy a poner
in genius because it seems to me that he transmits
en genio porque me parece que transmite
a lot in his video he transmits a lot of
mucho en su vídeo transmite mucha
energy you can see that he's passionate about what he
energía se nota que le apasiona lo que
does and besides he looks very fresh
hace y además es que se le ve muy fresco
that ease if I command it is that I am a
esa facilidad si que mando es que soy un
boomer and if you give me a new bm I
boomer y como me deis un bm nuevo lo
burn it that's what happens to me the
quemó eso es lo que me pasa en el
moment I understand a top I burn it
momento que entiendo un tope me lo quemó
and I tell you 27 times in the same video there
y te lo digo 27 veces en el mismo vídeo
will be a play of course this and it
habrá un play por supuesto esto y me
seems to me that he is going to be the only one that
parece que va a ser el único que
quite you already know that I sincerely have
bastante ya sabéis que yo sinceramente
not sucked determined by the style you
no he chupado determinada por el estilo
know that I have a lot of
ya sabéis que yo le tengo muchísimo
appreciation for him aura and it is
aprecio aura y es
sincerely I admire him very much and for
sinceramente lo admiro muchísimo y por
nothing  it's as much as youtube as a person he
nada es tanto como youtube como persona
seems like a top caliph to me it
me parece un top califa
seems to me I don't want
me parece haber tampoco quiero que los
youtubers if anything if they read this
youtubers si acaso si acaso leyera este
video to take it as an offense no
vídeo que se lo tome como una ofensa no
I'm criticizing what
yo estoy criticando lo que a mí me
seems to me the truth is that tariff I
parece a mí la verdad que tarifa yo
visited a video and tariff and I think it's
visitaba un vídeo y tarifa y me parece
bad I have nothing personal against
malo no tengo nada personal en contra de
him but it seems bad to me because because I
él pero me parece malo porque porque me
get into his videos they don't tell me anything they
meto en sus vídeos no me dicen nada me
seem like pure filler and sincerely I
parecen puro relleno y sinceramente yo
believe that sincerely if it weren't for his
creo que sinceramente si no fuera por su
last one I wouldn't be where he is still let's
última no estaría donde está quieto a
see I feel I had a fight with him that
ver siento yo tuve una bronca con él que
was true the [ __ ] no in fact I think there are
fue verdad la chorrada no de hecho creo
videos out there it is not syndicated to
que hay vídeos por ahí no se sindica a
that vital point it seems to me that the attitude
ese punto vital me parece que la actitud
of guys many times he wants to
de chicos muchas ocasiones quiere
do it as a joke but many
hacerlo como que de coña pero muchas
times he goes too far with the joke but the truth is
veces se pasa con la coña pero la verdad
that for me he did something in which for
que para mí hizo una cosa en la que para
me I take my hat off because he knew how to
mí me quito el sombrero porque supo
apologize or rather we had the argument and he
disculparse o sea tuvimos el rifirrafe y
knew how to apologize but that does not mean that
supo disculparse pero eso no quita que
as a youtuber I think it's horrible like
como youtuber me parezca horrible como
youtube he feels that he uploads and when he
youtube el siento que sube y cuando hace
streams he's no longer shooter he seems more
streaming ya no shooter me parece más
decent to me  you see
decente lo ve tú
what other people's are like and how
de lo que es el de los demás y qué
true that I have put on some videos of
verdad que me he puesto algún vídeo de
schutter and although many people do not
schutter y aunque a mucha gente no le
like this type of content but I
gusta este tipo de contenido pero yo lo
see him as a kid he gets involved talking he
veo de chaval se enrolla hablar se
gets involved against something he talks to you with the
enrolla contra otra cosa te habla con la
camera and such and it happened to me he was watching
cámara y tal y me ha pasado está viendo
a video of his and another one came up
un vídeo de él y que me salte otro
because this one saw here spending the night
porque éste vio aquí echando la noche
eating a seed and it brings me several
comiendo una pipa y me trae varios
videos in a row so the truth is that I
vídeos seguidos así que la verdad que yo
would say that this kid is decent, I find him
diría que decente este chaval me parece
indifferent more than anything because he does not
indiferente más que nada porque no se
have dallas he seems to me he seems like a
tiene dallas me parece me parece un
genius look at what the genius puts
genio mira no lo que pone el genio
because people are not going to say that he is my
porque la gente no va a decir que es mi
friend but the thing is that he knows very well
amigo pero es que es que sabe muy bien
I go for the genius and I do not give a damn
yo voy a por el genio y me suda todo
when it matters what people say I am going
cuando importa lo que diga la gente voy
to explain why it is that he has a
a explicar por qué es que tiene una
mentality very similar to mine and he knows
mentalidad muy parecida a la mía y sabe
very well how to do his job the content
muy bien hacer su trabajo el contenido
may seem that when he gets into salt
puede parecer que cuando se mete en sal
you may find it toxic whatever you want but
se os parezca tóxico lo que queráis pero
the videos are entertaining the videos
los vídeos están entretenidos los vídeos
are very well edited the guy lived it
están muy bien editados el tío lo vivía
recording the videos and he is upset he is
grabando los vídeos y está alterado está
upset if they are  high to have under the
alterado si están elevados tener bajo el
sky live mind that is recording and you have to
cielo vive mente que está grabando y hay
know how to recognize that he knows how to run the
que saber reconocer que sabe llevar el
business forward whether if he has to burn
negocio adelante sea si tiene que quemar
a video and he has to do an
un vídeo y tiene que hacer una
interview with Juan de Dios Pantoja and
entrevista a juan de dios pantoja y en
instead of uploading it in one track I lie he has to
vez subirla en una pista miento lo tiene
upload it in five parts
que subir en cinco partes
how the sub should be in five parts and
cómo debe ser la sub en cinco partes y
if he has to make a good
si se tiene que sacar un buen video de
20 minute video of two tweets he takes them out and to
20 minutos de dos tweets se los saca y a
me that seems like an artist I think
mí eso me parece de ser un artista creo
this Dario
que éste darío
Dario from me I wouldn't qualify him as a genius
darío de mí no lo calificaría como genio
but he seems pretty decent this
pero me parece bastante decente este
guy doesn't have a digi mario let's see I'm going to do
chico no se tiene digi mario a ver voy a
just you know there was a
hacer justo ya sabes que hubo una
controversy continue I think
polémica continuar yo me parece un
the fandom that has the
hipócrita el fandom que tiene el
primary
primario
[Music] is a hypocrite I'm
[Música]
sorry I know I'm going to earn a lot of
lo siento sé que me voy a ganar muchos
islay by making this video but
islay haciendo este vídeo pero
honestly like youtube it doesn't seem
sinceramente como youtube no me parece
bad to me I see that he knows how to entertain
malo yo veo que sabe entretener a la
people sweet and of the
peña dulce y de la mente bien
indifferent mind I know he has made many
indiferente sé que ha cometido muchas
mistakes but the truth is they are different
cagadas pero la verdad tienen diferente
because it doesn't seem like it's worth asking for
porque tampoco me parece como para pedir
his head
su cabeza
the best you shouldn't have been
el mejor tampoco
following him for long but it
debes siguiéndolo mucho tiempo pero sí
is true that lately I have  I've
que es verdad que últimamente me he
eaten a lot of your content and I'm going to
comido mucho su contenido y lo voy a
put it in decent I tell you the same thing, I mean
meter en decente os digo lo mismo o sea
when he had the controversy is where he
cuando cuando tuvo la polémica está en
began to criticize Dallas because he
la que empezó a criticar a dallas porque
messed with his father and I thought he was a
se metió con su papá y me pareció un
hypocrite and more after he was
hipócrita y más después de que estuvo
with 38 thousand viewers in a live
con 38 mil espectadores en un directo
without speaking Jordi the child already sincerely
sin habla jordi el niño ya sinceramente
seems horrible to me I do not understand
me parece horrible yo no entiendo a la
people when they get into a meme and they put
gente cuando le da por un meme y ponen
things like deifying deifying the
las cosas cómo endiosar endiosar a los
youtube and the influences because it is
youtube y a los influencias porque está
fashionable and because it is the one I average a thousand
de moda y porque es el me media mil
sincerely well I watch the videos
sinceramente pues yo me visto los vídeos
and it seems that it is to see the frog Gustav in
y parece que es a ver la rana gustavo en
any chapter of 'sesame street' it
cualquier capítulo de 'barrio sésamo' me
transmits to me more than I do the child already I
transmite más que yo el del niño ya yo
see him there with the tail here and everything does not
lo veo ahí con el cola acá y todo no
speak is not funny he is a
habla no tiene gracia es un
scarecrow we have come here to the
espantapájaros está hemos venido aquí al
sky channel oliveira we came here to
canal de sky oliveira hemos venido aquí
do with this stick it seems to me I do not
a hacer con este stick me parece no me
like his content but it seems to me a
gusta su contenido pero me parece un
genius because because I am going to value how he
genio porque porque voy a valorar cómo
works and he has known very well to hit the
trabaja y ha sabido muy bien dar en el
nail on the head with his content and knows how to
clavo con su contenido y sabe saber
touch the key to succeed look done
tocar la tecla para triunfar mira hecho
this already seems like a shame to me, even a
esto ya me parece una vergüenza incluso
question
pregunta
in my favor, I know that there are many people who would
a mi favor sé que hay mucha gente que lo
consider him a genius, my personal opinion would be that
consideraría genio mi opinión personal
he is decent, I'd consider him a
yo lo meterían decente yo tanto como un
genius, I don't know that in reality what is
genio no sé que en realidad lo que viene
being the little that is seen, he owes a lot to
siendo lo poquito ver le debe mucho a
Joel, no and that in fact that like that
joel no y que de hecho esa como esa
community will not be the same, Syrian he would not have
comunidad no será lo mismo sirio él no
existed but honestly to me
hubiera existido pero sinceramente a mí
today I consider him decent,
a día de hoy yo lo considero decente
horrible, fat, horrible, Paula, well,
horrible gordo horrible paula bueno
decent in terms of seriousness, Greg, I put him in the top
decente de grave de greg lo meto en top
the same, I think he is a guy who has
lo mismo me parece un tío que tiene un
incredible charisma in front of the camera, he
carisma delante de la cámara increíble
transmits a good vibe in his videos,
transmite un buen rollo en sus vídeos
which are the ones you admire, about Greve, he has
que son las que admiras de greve tiene
something that Euro Play also has, he
una cosa que también la tiene euro play
can record a video talking to you about
puede grabar un vídeo hablándote sobre
the air that comes in, stuffed in a bag
el aire que entra relleno en una bolsa
of potato chips and they eat up the whole 10
de patatas fritas y te comen los 10
minutes with the chips, they eat up
minutos enteros con las patatas te comen
the whole 10 minutes with the chips
los 10 minutos enteros con las patatas
because he knows how to communicate [ __ ] well,
porque que sabe comunicar de [__] madre
to me, salsa side and I think it's bad, okay, I'm not
a mi salsa side y me parece malo vale no
going to say horrible either, but I think it's
lo voy a poner horrible tampoco pero me
bad, it seems to me that he has the same
parece malo me parece que tiene lo mismo
as always, I say that there are many people who
de siempre digo que hay mucha gente que
take some influence as a
coge en alguna influencia como una
joke and as a meme  and they put it in the
gracia y como un meme y lo ponen en los
most
más
and to me honestly the videos of alzas
y a mí sinceramente los vídeos de alzas
and the jokes he makes and the humor he
y los chistes que hace y el humor que
has seems bad to me and if I was going to go
tiene me parece mal y si iba a ir a
despite the fact that I recently
pesar de que de que hace poco los
criticized them for the controversy that had to
critique por la polémica que tuvo
tell it to me I have seen
contarla a mí yo he visto los vídeos de
ibai's videos it seems to me not so much
ibai me parece que no tanto
because the truth is I have said this
porque la verdad yo lo he dicho esto
lately and seeing his videos that
últimamente y viendo sus vídeos que lo
summarizes his channel and realize in the
resume su canal y daros cuenta en los
videos that ibai records they are not videos
vídeos que graba ibai no son vídeos
recorded with a script and anything, I mean those
grabados con guión y nada o sea esos
videos spontaneously on camera
vídeos en espontáneamente en la cámara
in the live ones are pieces of
en los directos son trozos de directo de
edited live not as a premiere of his life on
editado no como estreno de su vida en
this occasion and it is funny if he
esta ocasión y es que tiene gracia si le
dubbed it it seems quite decent to me
dobló me parece bastante decente
lately he is doing less
últimamente está haciendo menos
constant than it was in the past I know
constantes de lo que era en el pasado sé
that he has worked very hard to
que se lo ha currado muchísimo para
get to where he is thanks youtube is
llegar a donde está gracias youtube es
quite decent I think it should be
bastante decente creo que debería
renewed a bit because I think
renovarse un poco porque creo que se
the number is getting a little stagnant
está quedando un poquillo estancado el
but it remains stagnant in the type
número pero sigue estancado en el tipo
of things they do as if he does not
de cosas que hacen como que no se le
come up with new things that the md show is not worth it
ocurren cosas nuevas que no vale el md
sincerely he is not one of the youtubers
show sinceramente no es de los youtuber
that I like the best
que mejor me caen vale por ciertas
they fall okay for certain hypocrisies that I consider they have been given in fact I made some videos but I have to recognize that the kid has a lot of talent his talent and he is very funny I feel very identified with his humor decent student and genius I'm going to put him in genius because I think he deserves to
poner en genio porque creo que se merece
be higher than some of those who
estar más alto que algunos de los que
are here okay there is so much gameplay look I
están aquí vale hay tan gameplay mira me
am totally indifferent right now you
es indiferente totalmente ahora mismo
know I don't think he is a bad youtuber but
sabe no me parece mal youtuber pero
we go back to the same thing he is not a youtuber
volvemos a lo mismo no es un youtuber
that tells me nothing absolutely nothing
que no me dice nada absolutamente nada
jaime lozano is a genius there are dead people
jaime lozano es un genio hay muertos o
or rather he has not made two documentaries on youtube let's see any [ __ ] master I like him very much I get along very well with him but honestly dude don't get angry I know that people watch my videos a lot but as youtube don't get angry please but I'm being digestive jordi maybe in some videos I could
jordi gual en algunos vídeos lo podría
put him in decent but I have a thorn
poner en decente pero tengo una espinita
stuck with him for the michael
clavada con él por el vídeo de michael
jackson video and for the amazon video
jackson y por el vídeo de la amazona
just for those two videos jordi I
solamente por esos dos vídeos jordi yo
'm going to put you [ __ ] scheme the
te voy a meter [__] esquema los
punishments are that bad  put it here on the
castigos es que malos meterlo aquí en el
same level that I'm going to leave you
mismo nivel que te voy a dejar
indifferent Jordi and I'm there to
indiferente jordi y estoy allí por
put you in reality
meterte en realidad
because apart from the fact that they make the videos
porque aparte de que hacen los vídeos
without informing you as you have said on
sin informarte como tú bien han dicho en
many occasions in five minutes you
muchas ocasiones en cinco minutos te
go to Google and find whatever
metes en google y encuentras lo que sea
to talk to us you stop us from making a
para hablarnos nos para tú a hacer un
video with the reach that it has I should take
vídeo con el alcance que tiene debería
advantage of it to see you documented
aprovecharlo para verte documentado
super well and have made pieces of
súper bien y haber hechos pedazos de
video about the person like the one
vídeo sobre la persona como el que hizo
Joan Plana or Dallas made because I
joan plana o dallas que porque mucha
get along well with many people but let's
gente me llevo bien con ellos pero es
be honest the Dallas video
que seamos sinceros el vídeo de dallas
about the mass a form taken from rap and
sobre la masa una forma sacada de rap y
then Jordi I think that many times you
luego jordi yo creo que muchas veces
force the issue of your attitude and we must
fuerzas el tema de tu actitud y hay que
respect women we must respect
respetar las mujeres hay que respetar a
everyone and I think that you Jordi
todo el mundo y yo creo que tú jordi
turn off the camera maybe I'm wrong
apagar la cámara a lo mejor me equivoco
but I think that you turn off the camera
pero yo creo que tú apagan la cámara
says
dice
[Music]
[Música]
actually
en realidad
Josemi friends yes to me he seems like a very good
josemi amigos si a mí me parece muy buen
guy obviously in the decent he is not
muchacho obviamente en el decente no es
a person that I am indifferent to
una persona que me sea indiferente
either he knows I know that Josemi's numbers
tampoco sabe sé que los números de
right now are not the best
josemi ahora mismo no son los mejores
but it's that  these are youtube streaks
pero es que estos son rachas de youtube
be the same now josemi decides to
sea lo mismo ahora josemi le da por
play another game tomorrow and that egg
jugar mañana a otro juego y ese huevo
hit the jackpot guys this is growing on me don't even
pegó un pelotazo tíos se me crece esto
ask it's not that look another
ni se pregunta no es que mira otra
redhead I would put it as horrible it's bad
pelirrojo lo pondría en horrible es malo
in reality it's not even in hypocrites there should be
en realidad es ni en hipócritas debería
another category here that was
haber aquí otra categoría que fuese
hypocritical but no I think that with the ones we
hipócrita pero no yo creo que con las
have we have enough needless to say
que tenemos tenemos bastante sobra decir
that it is paid for in reality then there would
que se lo paga en realidad entonces iba
be a lot of people who come to this
a haber mucha gente que venga a este
video and do not know me but just in case let it be
vídeo y no me conozca pero por si acaso
known that here on this channel the
que se sepa que aquí en este canal los
allies are the typical youtubers who
aliados son los típicos youtubers que se
want to get too too
quieren poner demasiado demasiado
moralistic in front of the public no I am
moralistas de cara al público no yo soy
the most progressive in the world here but then
aquí el más progre del mundo pero luego
then as if you are here black
luego como que estés acá negro
this is the one or panic and period okay and if it
este es el o pánico y punto vale y si
is black it is the or stop I am not
está negro es el o para no estoy
saying that this one stops it and whoever has the
diciendo que éste se lo para y el que
balls to tell me that this one does not stop it, upload
tenga [__] de decirme que éste no se
here challenge me dog
lo para que suba aquí retarme perro
Lolito the one who is very good Lolito is a
lolito el que hay muy bien lolito es
man waited as long as a genius Lolito
hombre esperó tanto como un genio lolito
not so much
no tanto
I would say that it is fine no look here we have
yo diría que está bien no mira aquí
a genius  I praised the achievements I
tenemos un genio elogió los logros me
think he is one of the masters of youtube in
parece uno de los amos de youtube en
some points he was not games his
algunos puntos no estaba juegos sus
opinions and things like that but come on it
opiniones y cosas así pero vamos me
seems to me that or even I am like this to
parece que o incluso estoy así así por
put it in the top okay I am not going to put it
meterlo en el top vale no lo voy a meter
in the top because I am going to value the fact that they are
en el top porque voy a valorar el hecho
not touching the
de que de que no están tocando las
indicated keys to exploit
teclas indicadas para explotar en
light on youtube its decent to my maximum it
youtube luz su decente a mi máxima me
seems decent I know that you are not going to
parece decente yo sé que no vais a estar
agree with me on this many
muy de acuerdo conmigo en esto mucha
people but it seems decent to me I
gente pero a mí me parece decente yo
have no problem as I do
tengo ningún problema como yo lo hago
criticisms I make criticisms on my channel
críticas yo le hago críticas en mi canal
but they are criticisms from humor but the thing is
pero son críticas desde el humor pero es
that I have nothing against the
que yo no tengo nada en contra del
content of the machine does not mess with
contenido de máquina no se mete con
anyone the boy has a crocodile in the
nadie el chaval tiene un cocodrilo en la
pool he has sharks in the pool and
piscina tiene tiburones en la piscina y
chabab to his roll entertainment to his
chabab a su rollo entretenimiento a su
people in my image I find it bad I
gente a mi imagen me parece malo yo
only angels that would not be granted
solamente ángeles que sería no concedían
and only if it were not for the blonde there is no
y sólo si no fuera por el rubio no ha de
mieres I will look to see how influences
mieres miraré a ver cómo influences
sincerely I am not going to put it in
sinceramente no la voy a poner en
horrible because I believe that in its time
horrible porque yo creo que en su tiempo
and I have said this a lot of times
y esto lo he dicho un montón de veces
you know that I am not lying that I considered that
sabéis que no miento que consideró que
the girl when she gave it  cane to her
la chavala cuando le daba caña a su
channel when she was constant and considered
canal cuando era constante y consideró
that she worked very hard on her channel and
que trabajaba muchísimo en su canal y
that if she hadn't deviated
que si no se hubiera desviado
I think she could have gone very high
creo que podría haber llegado muy alto
but I'm going to give her a bad rating because
pero la voy a poner en malo porque ahora
right now sincerely as an influence she is not
mismo sinceramente como influencia no
contributing much what they tell me about
está aportando mucho lo que me dicen de
the community that has a party what
la comunidad que tiene fiesta lo que
she as an influence does
ella como influencia
not matter that we are fighting at the
no importa que estemos peleados de
door what has happened nothing ok jagger
puerta lo que haya pasado nada ok jagger
indifferent it does not seem bad to me neither does it
indiferentes no me parece malo tampoco
have this boom the unknown and
tiene este boom el mundo desconocido y
so unknown world look for when they put it
tan desconocido busca cuando lo pongan
in different
en diferente
I am going to put the touch it is the
yo lo voy a poner el toque es el
youtuber that I like the most when u2 see
youtuber que más me gusta cuando u2 ver
what the problem is and why I almost do not
cuál es el problema y por el que casi no
put it in all well the problem is
lo pongo en todos pues el problema es
that the bastard is very lazy does not want to
que el cabrón es muy vago no quiere
upload videos when he uploads videos for me he
subir vídeos cuando sube vídeos para mí
is the best show consumer I am
es el mejor show consumer me es
indifferent in fact who they are pantomime
indiferente hecho quién son pantomima
full decent this is a genius my daddy
full decente este sea un genio mi papi
gabi this is a genius good person a
gabi este sea un genio buena persona un
heart that does not fit in his chest and I am
corazón que no le cabe en el pecho y me
very happy with how he is doing right now
alegro muchísimo de cómo le va ahora
I have been following him since the 30
mismo yo llevo siguiéndolo desde los 30
thousand followers he had when I
mil seguidores que tenía cuando le
met him and this kid has cost him, it has
conocí y este chaval le ha costado le ha
cost him  his back what he has for
costado su espalda lo que tiene por
ferré I'm going to leave it as decent I know that a
ferré lo voy a dejar en decentes sé que
lot of people criticize him a lot but to
mucha gente que lo critica mucho pero a
me it's not work I think he makes
mí no es trabajar me parece que hace
good videos the pechito a while ago I
buenos vídeos el pechito hace un tiempo
would have put it in bad but
lo hubiera puesto en malos pero
honestly he has recovered quite a bit with
sinceramente ha remontado bastante con
what he is doing now especially
con lo que está haciendo ahora sobre
with terror plate as one factor I'm not
todo
going to put it bad because I've seen some of
voy a poner malo porque he visto algún
his videos about the youtube algorithm
vídeo suyo sobre el algoritmo de youtube
talking about things that more interested
que hablando cosas que más interesados
that have seemed good to me is that he
que me han parecido bueno es que las
knows them what happens is that I don't like him
sabe que lo que pasa que no me cae bien
but I'm going to put it decent because I'm going to be
pero lo voy a poner decente porque voy a
objective with his content to me
hacer objetivo con su contenido a mi
revealing I like it I think he has
revelando me gusta me parece que tiene
a horrible sense of humor ricky eddie was a
un humor horrible ricky eddie fue un
genius at the time I'm not going to leave the
genio en la época no voy a dejar el
decent just because of that it's an
decente solamente por eso sea una
imagination that shits you steal the
imaginación que te cagas roben las
rules put decent I don't think it's bad there
reglas ponen decente no me parece mala
's no roma gallardo either I don't share his
tampoco hay roma gallardo no comparto su
ideology but I think he's a genius we have
ideología pero me parece un genio hemos
reacted in fact to many of his videos
reaccionado de hecho a muchos vídeos
look I think he's a genius just
suyos mira me parece un genio solamente
because of the interviews on the street the
por las entrevistas en la calle las
interviews about who he would vote for and the
entrevistas sobre a quién votaría y las
interviews about feminism just for
entrevistas del feminismo solamente por
that for me he has earned that position he
eso para mí se ha ganado ese puesto
has other videos in which you could
tiene otros vídeos en los que se podrían
take the position of alia
llevar el puesto de alía de
perfectly his idol was julio anguita
perfectamente su ídolo era julio anguita
and he says he would vote we can vote now
y él dice que votaría podemos votar ya
we can if he had to choose between
podemos si tuviera que elegir entre
other parties but well he considers him
otros partidos pero bueno lo considera
a genius okay I'm staying with his content
un genio vale me quedo con su contenido
the truth is that spent many hours
la verdad que pasado muchísimas horas
going through this it is indisputable
pasando esto es indiscutible
although he did not leave being honest rubio is
aunque no se fue siendo sincero rubio es
observant I already think it's bad bad and
observadora ya me parece malo malo y
leaning towards horrible the boy is
tirando para horrible el chico esté
saved it seems to me also
salva me parece también
because I don't know if I should put the horrible ones look
pues no sé si poner los horribles fíjate
what I'm telling you it seems horrible
lo que te digo me parece horrible hace
two videos ago I don't believe
dos vídeos detrás no me creo que esté
my success is here I don't believe he's here
aquí mi éxito no me creo que esté aquí
in this position he became a genius on me
en este puesto se me puso un genio
also look at how he expelled papi gavin
también fíjate que expulsó a papi gavin
there he put him topless I don't put them in
ahí lo ponía en topless no los pongo en
everything yet because they have not hit what is being
todo todavía porque tampoco han pegado
the explosion look
lo que viene siendo la explosión mira
for example because still the and because look
por ejemplo porque aún los y porque mira
for the if he came out of the [ __ ] way you would
por los si él les saliera del [__] os
already have millions and millions of
lo estaría ya millones y millones de
subscribers if there was a video or not it's
suscriptores si se hubiese vídeo o no es
a channel that can go five months without
un canal que puede estar cinco meses sin
uploading content that suddenly uploads a
subir contenido que de repente sube un
video it starts trending and the
vídeo se pone en tendencia y tiene el
video has half a million views look with
vídeo medio millón de visitas busca con
youtuber what happens to that having the
youtuber que le pase eso teniendo el
channel abandoned half a year
canal abandonado medio año
now a secondary channel is created and I think it
ahora se crea un canal secundario y creo
will surpass the main one of this
que va a superar al principal de este
guy
chico
he deserves to be genius being
él se merece están genio siendo
realistic I do not agree with his ideals and I
realistas no comulgo con sus ideales y
do not agree with many of his
no comulgo con su muchas de sus
opinions but honestly his content
opiniones pero sinceramente su contenido
seems to me it seems that he deserves this
me parece me parece que merece esta
category he is terrible and quite
categoría es terrible y párraco bastante
decent even in some jokes I would put him
decente incluso en algunas bromas lo
in genius I am going to leave it in
metería en genio lo voy a dejar en
decent but there have been many jokes with
decente pero ha habido muchas bromas con
which I have laughed a lot look at
las que me he reído muchísimo mira
vegeta this I did not know there were going to be so many
vegeta esto no sabía que iba a haber
then it is for me together I have
tantos entonces está para mí juntos yo
met him and besides he is a guy who
lo he conocido y aparte es un tío que me
seems humble to me after the numbers he
parece humilde después de los números
has he seems to me a very good person very
que tiene me parece muy buena persona
nice very pleasant he does not mess
muy simpático muy agradable no se mete
with anyone
con nadie
vegetables leaders in situ watch youtube of
vegetales leaders in situ ver youtube de
a guy that I really like okay in a
un chico que me cae muy bien vale en un
guy that I really like I am going to
chico que me cae de [__] madre lo voy a
put him in decent although I say that he would be
poner en decente aunque digo que sería
decent leaning towards genius but I am going to
decente tirando para genio pero lo voy a
put him in decent because to me the
poner en decente porque a mí el
content he makes is more focused on
contenido que hace está más centrado en
football and you know that I am very
el fútbol y ya sabéis que yo estoy muy
detached from that no then I am not going to
despegado de eso no entonces no lo voy a
leave it in decent because it seems to me that
dejar en decente porque me parece que
the videos that  you do what
está bastante bien los vídeos que haces
happens that I don't love it,
lo que pasa que a mí no me encanta
look what a little bag he also plays
fíjate qué bolsito también se dedica al
football a lot but he also records things from time to
fútbol mucho pero también graba de vez
time
en cuando
and it entertains me a lot more as does
cosas y a mí me divierte mucho más al
papi gabino who is also
igual que papi gabino que también está
quite focused on football lately
bastante centrar el fútbol últimamente
but obviously has much more william
pero obviamente tiene mucho más william
quite decent TV also pellón very
tele bastante decente además pellón muy
good with him I would put willy clock in
bien con él yo a willy reloj pondría en
decent god see you being fair and
decentes dios os ver siendo justos y
exposed here to the blond because together I would
expuesto aquí al rubios porque ya juntos
also have to put him but the
también lo tendría que poner a él pero
truth is that the blond
es que sinceramente es que el rubio me
seems to me that sometimes makes
parece que hacer algunas veces vídeos
funnier videos than willy man that willy
más divertidos que willy tío que willy
who plays the point is that willy does not
que juega el punto es que willy no se
complicate his life at
complica la vida para nada bueno tampoco
all well I am not much very much infinitely much better than will and then he explains what a horrible god team and he also after entering football they would put it decent okay of the monthly payment of total mar and nobody to see the content of marina yesterday in sticks I like
de marina ayer en palos me cae muy bien
the girl very much I like the girl
la chica es me cae muy bien la chica
very well very well very well neither
está muy bien muy bien muy bien tampoco
freezers but I do not dislike it to me
congeladores pero que no me cae mal a mí
I find it funny so she talks a lot of
me parece graciosa así que habla mucha
nonsense and such but she says  to me it gives
tontería y tal pero pone a mí me da
content for videos there it will be
contenido para vídeos ahí va a ser
grace marin yesterday it seems very bad to me that she
gracia marín ayer me parece muy mal que
was unfaithful to her boyfriend at a party in
fuera infiel a su novio en una fiesta
front of a lot of influence where they
delante de mucho influencia donde la
could record her and the recorder bothers her
podían grabar y la grabadora le estorba
my ways I have a conflict with just
mis formas tengo un conflicto con solo
paper and there are videos with which I have
papel y es que hay vídeos con los que me
laughed but there are videos in which it has
he reído pero hay vídeos en los que
even seemed to me a little quality
incluso me ha parecido un poco calidad
then there have been videos that seem
luego ha habido vídeos que me parecen
terrible to me I sincerely on many
malísimos yo sinceramente en muchas
occasions I think it has a very
ocasiones creo que tiene un humor muy
easy humor I am not going to put it bad days on the
fácil no lo voy a poner malos días en el
subject of the edition that is missing on purpose
tema de la edición que falta a propósito
the q3 evolved not so much as bad it
el q3 evolucionó no tanto como malo no
is not that I am remembering good video
es que me estoy acordando de vídeo bueno
but it is that I would not put it that
pero es que yo no lo pondría que
indecent in the same category native
indecente en la misma categoría nativa
racó and avid uber not a chance you know in
racó y avid uber ni de coña sabes de
fact it seems to me that more and more it deserves to
hecho me parece que más y más merece
be higher than the mirasol more we are going to
estar más alto que el mirasol más vamos
stay in part already put in different
a quedar en parte ya poner en diferente
okay churra and I roll with you and well
vale churra y me enrollo contigo y bueno
guys I know that this video will raise
chavales se que este vídeo a levantar
quite a few blisters I know that many
bastante ampollas sé que a muchos no les
will not like my opinion seemed as
va a gustar mi opinión parecido lo más
sincere as possible in my opinion just
sincero posible en mi opinión al igual
as I did not agree with
que yo no estaba de acuerdo con muchas
many other lists that other youtubers have made but it's on mine ok and nothing I'm going to be reading you, yes in the comments box subscribe if you liked my channel give it a like so my content is recommended a lot and see you in the next video
y nos vemos en el siguiente vídeo
[Music]
[Música]